James Earle and Laura Gardin Fraser Papers
James Earle and Laura Gardin Fraser Papers
- Designs and reproductions
  - Fraser, James Earle
    - Medals
      - Williams College (Box 23)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 69.
      - Yale University Howland Memorial (Box 23)
    - Sculpture
      - Albright, Joseph J. and Elizabeth, memorial (Box 23)
      - "Amazon" (Box 23)
      - Animals (Box 23)
      - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Box 23)
      - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Box 24)
      - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Box 25)
      - Arlington Memorial Bridge (oversize) (Oversize 13)
      - "Aviator" (Box 25)
      - Bacon, Robert, bust (Box 25)
      - "Basque" (Box 25)
      - Bear (Box 25)
      - Brewster, Horatio Hathaway, relief (Box 25)
        See also Glass negatives inOversize 23.
      - "The Buffalo Herd" (Box 25)
      - "The Buffalo Prayer" (Box 25)
      - "Canadian Officer" (Box 25)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 69-70
      - "Canadian Officer" (oversize) (Oversize 8)
      - Caricatures (Box 25)
      - Chase, J. Eastman, bust (Box 25)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 70-71.
      - "Cheyenne Warrior" (Box 25)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 71.
      - Chicago University Club, relief (Box 25)
      - Children, busts (Box 25)
      - Cleveland, Grover, memorial (Box 25)
      - "Dancer" (Box 25)
      - Debs, Eugene V., relief (Box 25)
      - Delano, Warren, bust (Box 25)
      - Deming, E.W., bust (Box 25)
      - Deming, Henrietta, bust (Box 25)
      - Denys, Rev. F. Ward, sarcophagus (Box 25)
      - Denys, Rev. F. Ward, sarcophagus (Box 26)
      - Edison, Thomas Alva, bust (Box 26)
      - Edison, Thomas Alva, seated figure; 4 folders (Box 26, 27)
      - Edison, Thomas Alva, seated figure (oversize) (Oversize 16)
      - Edison Tower (Box 27)
      - Elks Club National Memorial, "Charity," "Fidelity," "Justice," "Brotherly Love" figures (Box 27)
      - "End of the Trail" (Box 27)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 72.
      - "End of the Trail" (oversize) (Oversize 13)
      - Ericson, David Barnard, relief (Box 27)
        See also Glass negatives in Oversize 27.
      - Ericson, John, memorial; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Ericson, John, memorial (Box 28)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 72-73
      - Evans, June, bust (Box 28)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 73
      - Firestone, Harvey S., memorial; 4 folders (Box 28, 29)
      - Firestone, Harvey S., memorial (oversize) (Oversize 11)
      - Firestone, Harvey S., memorial (oversize) (Oversize 16)
      - "Forces That Ride the Earth" (Box 29)
      - Ford, Patrick, bust (Box 29)
      - Fountain (Box 29)
      - Fountain, E.H. Harriman Garden (Box 29)
      - Fountain, E.H. Harriman Garden (oversize) (Oversize 16)
      - Franklin, Benjamin, seated figure; 4 folders (Box 29, 30)
      - Franklin, Benjamin, seated figure (oversize) (Oversize 15)
      - Gaillard, David D., relief (Box 30)
      - Gallatin, Albert, standing figure; 6 folders (Box 30, 31)
      - Gallatin, Albert, standing figure (oversize) (Oversize 7)
      - Garner, John Nance, bust; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Gibson, Charles Dana, bust (Box 31)
      - Goodwin, Sage, bust (Box 31)
      - "Grief" (Box 31)
      - Hamilton, Alexander, standing figure; 2 folders (Box 31)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 73-74.
      - Hamilton, Alexander, standing figure (oversize) (Oversize 11)
      - Harriman, E.H., relief (Box 31)
      - Hay, John, memorial (Box 31)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 74.
      - Indian, bust (Box 31)
      - Indian, standing figure (Box 31)
      - Jefferson, Thomas, seated figure (Box 31)
      - Jefferson, Thomas (Missouri Memorial), standing figure; 3 folders (Box 32)
      - Jefferson, Thomas (Missouri Memorial), standing figure (oversize) (Oversize 1)
      - Jefferson, Thomas (Missouri Memorial), accompanying figures
        - Lewis and Clark (Box 32)
        - Lewis and Clark (oversize) (Oversize 16)
      - Jesup, Morris Ketchum, relief (Box 32)
      - "Journey Through Life" (Box 32)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 74-75.
      - Key, Francis Scott, memorial (Box 32)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 75.
      - LeDoux, Louis, bust (Box 32)
      - Lincoln, Abraham, seated figure; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Lincoln, Abraham, seated figure (Oversize 1)
      - Locke, George Lyman, relief (Box 33)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 75-76
      - Mask (Box 33)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 76
      - Mayo, Charles H. and William J., memorial; 3 folders (Box 34)
      - Mayo, Charles H. and William J., memorial (oversize) (Oversize 9)
      - "Melisande" (Box 34)
      - Michigan Avenue Bridge, Chicago, pylons
        - "Discoverers" and "Pioneers" (Box 34)
        - "Discoverers" and "Pioneers" (oversize) (Oversize 8)
      - Patton, George S. Jr., standing figure; 6 folders (Box 34, 35)
      - Patton, George S. Jr., standing figure (oversize) (Oversize 6)
      - Pegasus Group (Box 35)
      - "Pioneer Woman" (Box 35)
      - Pioneer Woman, rough Study? (Box 36)
      - Polk, William M., relief (Box 36)
      - Potter, Bishop Henry C., sarcophagus (Box 36)
      - Potter, Bishop Henry C., sarcophagus (oversize) (Oversize 2)
      - "Primitive Inventor of Water Power" (Box 36)
      - "Priscilla" (Box 36)
      - Rankin, bust (Box 36)
      - Riley, John, bust (Box 36)
      - Robinson, Edwin Arlington, memorial plaque (Box 36)
      - Roosevelt, Theodore, bust (Box 36)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 76-77.
      - Roosevelt, Theodore, bust (oversize) (Oversize 7)
      - Roosevelt, Theodore, death mask (Box 36)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 77.
      - Roosevelt, Theodore, equestrian figure; 7 folders (Box 36, 37)
      - Roosevelt, Theodore, equestrian figure (oversize) (Oversize 21)
      - Roosevelt, Theodore, with accompanying figures
        - Lewis, Clark, Audubon, and Boone, models, sketches, photos (Box 38)
        - Lewis, Clark, Audubon, and Boone, negatives (Box 86)
      - Roosevelt, Theodore, national monument (Box 38)
      - Roosevelt, Theodore, relief (Box 38)
      - Root, Elihu, bust; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Root, Elihu, bust (oversize) (Oversize 12)
      - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus, bust; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Schoellkopf, Henry, 2 folders; relief (Box 38)
      - Schoellkopf, M.H., bust (Box 38)
      - Second Division Memorial (Box 39)
      - Second Division Memorial (oversize) (Oversize 12)
      - "Storm Driven" (Box 39)
      - "Storm Driven" (oversize) (Oversize 16)
      - Taft, William Howard, memorial (Box 39)
      - U.S. Archives, pediment; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - U.S. Archives, pediment (oversize) (Oversize 17)
      - U.S. Archives, reliefs (Box 39)
      - U.S. Archives, seated figures "Guardian" and "Mother and Child" (Box 39)
      - U.S. Commerce Department, pediments (Box 40)
      - U.S. Supreme Court, seated figures; 4 folders (Box 40)
      - U.S. Supreme Court, seated figures (oversize) (Oversize 16)
      - Unknown Soldier, tomb (Box 40)
      - Unknown Soldier, tomb (oversize) (Oversize 17)
      - Urn (Box 40)
      - Urn (oversize) (Oversize 16)
      - "Venus de Meow Sleeping Cat", relief (Box 40)
      - "Victory" (Box 41)
        See also Glass negatives in Boxes 77-78.
      - "Victory" (oversize) (Oversize 8)
      - Virginia War Memorial (Box 41)
      - Washington, George, equestrian figure; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Washington, George, standing figure; 3 folders (Box 41)
      - Washington, George, standing figure (oversize) (Oversize 22)
      - Whitney Children, busts, reliefs; 3 folders (Box 42)
        See also Glass negatives in Oversize 23.
      - Whitney Children, busts, reliefs (oversize) (Oversize 16)
      - "Windswept" (Box 42)
      - "Young Artist", bust (Box 42)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 78.
      - "Young Artist", bust (oversize) (Oversize 2)
  - Fraser, Laura Gardin
    - Catalogues (Box 42)
    - Coins
      - Alabama Centennial half dollar (Box 42)
      - Grant, Ulysses S., half dollar (Box 42)
      - Liberty Dollar (Box 42)
      - MacArthur, Douglas, Phillipines one peso (Box 42)
      - Washington, George, quarter dollar (Box 42)
    - Medals
      - Air Medal (Box 42)
      - American Bar Association (Box 42)
      - American Geographical Society Centennial (Box 42)
      - Belleau Wood Memorial Association (Box 42)
      - "Better Babies" (Box 42)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 79.
      - Bide-A-Wee Home for Dogs (Box 42)
      - "Doctrina", See also Glass negatives in Box 79. (Box 42)
      - Franklin, Benjamin (Box 42)
      - International Livestock Exposition (Box 42)
      - Irish Setter Club of America (Box 42)
      - Lindbergh, Charles (Box 42)
      - Lindbergh, Charles (oversize) (Oversize 16)
      - Marshall, George C. (Box 42)
      - Massachusetts Tercentenary (Box 42)
      - Morgan Horse Club (Box 42)
      - National Geographic Society, Richard E. Byrd (Box 43)
      - National Geographic Society, Gilbert Grosvenor (Box 43)
      - National Geographic Society, Hubbard (Box 43)
      - Oklahoma Semi-Centennial (Box 43)
      - Peace of Versailles (Box 43)
      - Horse Association of America, polo (Box 43)
      - Smith, R. Penn Jr. (Box 43)
      - "Steady" (Box 43)
      - Thayer, Sylvanus (Box 43)
      - U.S. Army and Navy Chaplains (Box 43)
      - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 43)
      - U.S. Military Academy (West Point) sesquicentennial (Box 43)
      - "Vermont" (Box 43)
      - Walcott, Charles D. (Box 43)
      - Washington, George bicentennial (Box 43)
    - Sculpture
      - Acadia Mountain plaque (Box 43)
      - American history panels, relief (Box 43)
      - American history panels, relief (Box 44)
      - American History Panels, relief (oversize) (Oversize 18-20)
        #26 panel 3
        #27 panel 1
        #28 panel 2
      - Baby Goat (Box 44)
      - "Baby with Duck" (Box 44)
      - Bowman, Isaiah, bust (Box 44)
      - Creche, relief (Box 44)
      - Dog, cocker spaniel (Box 44)
      - Dog, foxhound (Box 44)
      - Dog, "Methuselah" (Box 44)
      - Dog, "Snuff" (Box 44)
      - Drinker, Henry Sturgis, relief (Box 44)
      - Duck (Box 44)
      - Elk, relief (Box 44)
      - Elk, statuary (Box 44)
      - Forbes, William Cameron, relief (Box 45)
      - Franklin, Benjamin, relief (Box 45)
      - "Goat Baby", statue (Box 45)
      - Golf Player, sundial (Box 45)
      - "Grape Baby", fountain (Box 45)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 80.
      - Harriman, Mary W., relief (Box 45)
      - Hartford Fire Insurance Company commemorative relief (modeled by Laura Gardin Fraser after Landseer), pair of cast bronze bookends created for the Hartford Fire Insurance Company to commemorate the 110th anniversary of its founding (Box 85)
      - Hitt, William F., memorial (Box 45)
      - Holloway, Frances Angeline, relief (Box 45)
      - Horse, "Citroen", polo pony trophy (Box 45)
      - Horse, "Fairplay" (Box 45)
      - Horse, "John" (Box 45)
      - Horse, "Miss Buck" (Box 45)
      - Horse, "Prince Friarstown" (Box 45)
      - Horse, "Trotting Filly" (Box 45)
      - Kilby, Thomas E., relief (Box 45)
      - Lee, Robert E. and "Stonewall" Jackson, equestrian figures; 4 folders (Box 45, 46)
      - Lee, Robert E. and "Stonewall" Jackson, equestrian figure (oversize) (Oversize 22)
      - "The Long Long Trail", relief (Box 46)
      - Lyon, Mary, bust (Box 46)
      - "Minotaur and Pans", statue (Box 46)
      - Navy Goat (Box 46)
      - "Nymph and Satyr" (Box 46)
        See also Glass negatives in Oversize 80.
      - "Oklahoma Run" (Box 46)
      - Pacific War Memorial, relief (Box 46)
      - "Peace with Justice" (Box 47)
      - "Pegasus", 2 folders (Box 47)
      - "Pegasus," 1977 accession, 3 folders (Box 47)
      - Theodore Roosevelt Bridge, reliefs "Courage," "Power," "Leadership," "Foresight"; 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Russell Memorial (Box 47)
      - "Simplicity" (Box 47)
      - Smith, Carol Harriman, relief (Box 47)
      - Smith, Rev. Cornelius B., relief (Box 47)
      - Smith, Eugene, bust (Box 47)
      - Stuart, Gilbert, bust (Box 47)
      - Tener, John Kinley, relief (Box 47)
      - Urn with Polo Players (Box 47)
        See also Glass negatives in Box 81.
      - U.S. House of Representives, reliefs (Box 47)
      - Washington, George, relief (Box 47)
      - Wrestlers, two figures (Box 47)
      - "Young Porker" (Box 47)
  - Fraser, James Earle and Laura Gardin
    - Coins
      - Oregon Trail Half Dollar (Box 48)
    - Medals
      - Sketches (Box 48)
      - Photographs and negatives (Box 48)
    - Sculpture
      - Models, 2 folders (Box 48)
      - Sketches, 7 folders (Box 48, 49)
      - Sketches (oversize) (Oversize 2)
      - Photographs (Box 49)
      - Negatives (Box 49)
        See also Glass negatives in Boxes 81-82.
  - Fraser, James Earle and T.H. Somes
    - Sculpture
      - Grant, Ulysses S., bust (Box 49)
  - Frémiet, E.
    - Sculpture (Box 49)
      See also Glass negatives in Box 82.
  - Gardin, Alice Tilton
    - Catalogs (Box 49)
  - Huntington, Alice Hyatt
    - Sculpture (Box 49)
  - Lane, Katherine W.
    - Sculpture (Box 49)
  - Laurie, Lee
    - Medals (Box 49)
  - MacMonnies, Frederick
    - Sculpture (Box 49)
  - Olesen, Olaf
    - Paintings (Box 49)
  - Rubins, David K.
    - Sculpture (Box 50)
  - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus
    - Sculpture
      - Adams Memorial (Box 50)
      - Diana, standing figure (Box 50)
      - Farragut, David G., standing figure (Box 50)
      - Lincoln, Abraham, standing figure (Box 50)
      - Lincoln, Abraham, standing figure (oversize) (Oversize 16)
      - Shaw Memorial (Box 50)
      - Sherman Memorial (Box 50)
  - Waugh, Sidney Biehler
    - Sculpture (Box 50)
  - Unidentified
    - Medals (Box 50)
    - Sculpture, 9 folders (Box 50)
      See also Glass negatives in Boxes 82-83.
    - Sketch
      - Robinson, Edwin Arlington (Box 50)
      - Robinson, Edwin Arlington (oversize) (Oversize 3)
  - Unknown
    - Architecture and Archeology (Box 50)
    - Architecture and Archeology (oversize) (Oversize 16)
    - Sculpture (Box 50)
- Memorabilia
  - General
    - Fraser, James Earle
      - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1927-1948 (Box 50)
      - Biographical material, 1929-1967 (Box 50)
      - Certificates and awards, 1918-1944 (Box 51)
      - Medals, 1915-1946; 2 folders (Box 51)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1909-1939; 6 folders (Box 51)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1940-1966; 4 folders (Box 52)
      - Notebooks, 1949 (Box 52)
      - Obituaries, 1953 (Box 52)
      - Passports, 1929-1949 (Box 52)
      - Scrapbook
        - on Theodore Roosevelt's death, 1919 (Box 52)
        - on Theodore Roosevelt's death (oversize) (Oversize 4)
      - Slides (Fraser Lantern Slide Collection), undated (Oversize 24)
        For complete list of slides, see Glass negatives in Oversize 24.
    - Fraser, Laura Gardin
      - Address book (Box 52)
      - Appointment books, 1912-1935 (Box 52)
      - Biographical material, 1919-1960 (Box 52)
      - Certificates and awards, 1944-1963 (Box 52)
      - Medals, 1926-1956; 2 folders (Box 52)
      - National achievement awards, 1930-1948; 2 folders (Box 53)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1920-1967; 5 folders (Box 53)
      - Notebooks, 1949-1960 (Box 53)
      - Obituaries, 1966 (Box 53)
      - Passports, 1929 (Box 53)
      - Scrapbook, Lee-Jackson statues (Box 53)
      - Scrapbook, Lee-Jackson statues (oversize) (Oversize 14)
    - Fraser, James Earle and Laura Gardin
      - Christmas cards, 1935-1938 (Box 53)
      - Ephemera
        - Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 53)
        - Honeymoon, 1913 (Box 54)
        - Invitations and programs, 1927-1959 (Box 54)
      - Films
        - Ann Harding and Joe Wheelwright, 1931; fraser_je_001; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 100 feet (Oversize 25)
        - Blank reel, undated; fraser_je_007; 16mm film, 100 feet (Oversize 25)
        - Havana, Jan 1929; fraser_je_009; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 150 feet (Oversize 25)
        - Ramdal Nov. 4, undated; fraser_je_008; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 100 feet (Oversize 25)
        - Setting J's Statue on Roosevelt Memorial/Equestrian (NY), 1934-1940; fraser_je_010; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 300 feet (Oversize 25)
        - Virginia, Eleanor, JEF and LGF, 1932; fraser_je_002; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 50 feet (Oversize 25)
        - Unidentified No. 1 (Military Academy), undated; fraser_je_003; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 100 feet (Oversize 25)
        - Unidentified No. 2 (Horse Sculpture), undated; fraser_je_004; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 100 feet (Oversize 25)
        - Unidentified No. 3 (Baby Reel), undated; fraser_je_005; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 25 feet (Oversize 25)
        - Unidentified No. 4 (Horse sculpture and bust), undated; fraser_je_006; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 100 feet (Oversize 25)
      - Audiorecordings
        - An Experience in Stereofonic Sound - Musical Excerpts from Concertapes Stereo Library, fraser_je_012; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - Eric and Lucia, fraser_je_017; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - Interview, WCVS, Springfield, Illinois, fraser_je_011; running time 14:00 minutes; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #1], fraser_je_013; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #2], fraser_je_014; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #3], fraser_je_015; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #4], fraser_je_016; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #5], fraser_je_018; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #6], fraser_je_019; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #7], fraser_je_020; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1935-1937; fraser_je_021; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1937-1939; fraser_je_022; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1939-1940; fraser_je_023; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1940; fraser_je_024; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1940-1941; fraser_je_025; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1941-1942; fraser_je_026; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], fraser_je_027; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1942-1943; fraser_je_028; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1944-1945; fraser_je_029; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1945-1946; fraser_je_030; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1946-1947; fraser_je_031; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1947-1948; fraser_je_032; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1949-1950; fraser_je_033; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1950-1952; fraser_je_034; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled], 1952-1953; fraser_je_035; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #8], fraser_je_036; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
          Side 1: Stars in My Eyes; Love Walked In; Where or When; The Touch of Your Hand; Oklahoma; Sunset [illegible]; Eastern Parade; Dancing in the Dark; Swanee River; Begin the Beguine; Smoke Gets In; Love Locked Out; Czardos; Sympathy; Crazy Rythm; The Clipper; [illegible]; Side 2: Sentimental Journey; Undecided; Everywhere You Go; Someone Like You; Forever and Ever; I Don’t See Me in Your Eyes Anymore; On the Outgoing Tide; Hush Little Darling; Happy Times; Again; My Dream to [illegible]; How Many Times Do I Have to Tell You; How Blue the Night; If You Were the Only Girl; Girl of My Dreams; Blue Skies; Star Dust; Hawaiian Sunset; If I Knew Then; I Wanna Go Home with You
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #9], fraser_je_037; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
          Side 1: I’ll Get By; Flatbush Flannigan; Daddy; Aurora; House in Boogie; Opus No. 1; Booglie [illegible] Piggy; Sunrise Boogie; Johnson Roy; Sherman Shuffle; Shine; Broggin’; Yes Indeed; Copley Square; Anvil Chorus; Smoke, Smoke, Smoke; I’m Gonna See My Baby; Tattletale; Bi-I-Bi; Who Wouldn’t Love You; Love Me a Little Little; Side 2: If You Are But a Dream; For Sentimental Reasons; You’ll Always Be the One Love; Moonlight Cocktail; You and I; Now is the Hour; A Bluebird Singing My Heart; It’s a Big Wide Wonderful World; I Get the Neck of the Chicken; Can’t Get Out of This Mood; Blueberry Hill; Maybe; Only Forever; How Do I Know It’s real; Blue Tail Fly; An Apple Blossom Wedding; Miss You; Skylark; Blue Shawdows and W. Gord; Dream; When am I Gonna Kiss You Good Morning
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #10], fraser_je_038; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
          Side 1:Tumbling Tumbleweeds; Cool Water; Wagon Wheels; Ol’ Man River; That Lucky Ole Sun; Ah Still Suits Me; St. Louis Blues; I Get the Blues When it Rains; Either It’s Love or it Isn’t; In the Cool of Evening; That [illegible] Feeling; Star Dust; Stormy Weather; Night and Day; Just One of Those Things; I See Your Face Before Me; A Pretty Girl is Like a Melody; All the Things You Are; I Got Rhythm; Star Dust; Intermetzo; Side 2: Going My Way; Swinging on a Star; I’m Thinking Tonight of My Blue Eyes; I Want My Mama; Why Don’t We Do This More Often; Nice Dreamin’ Baby; Crosstown; Falling Leaves; Moondust Rhapsody; Cabin in the Sky; Too Marvelous for Words; Ain’t Got a Dime to My Name; The Road to Morocco; Cocktails for Two; Leave the Dishes in the Sink Ma; Blue Bird of Happiness; When You’re a Long Long Way from Home; I Don’t Want to Walk Without You; Darling, je vous aime beaucoup; Be Careful It’s My Heart; Lazy
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #11], fraser_je_039; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
          Side 1: Andu Kastelantez; Motion Picture Fav.; 3 Singles; Musical Comedy Fav.; except the Touch of Your Hand; Side 2: Softly as in a Moon Sun; Jalousie; Besame Mucho; Dancing in the Dark; Tico, Tico; Ay, Ay, Ay; Espana Cani; Speak Low; Temptation; I’ve Got You Under My Skin; That Old Black Magic; The Very Thought of You; I Get a Rick Out of You; Dark Eyes; Dankey Serenade; Pavanne; Mazurka in B Flat; running time
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #12], fraser_je_040; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
          Side 1: Still, Still Still; Marianna; All Through the Night; Chick Got the Shears; The Fountain; Ebony; Aupies de ma blonde; Carmen, Carmen; Lift a Glass to Friendshi; Bambos Flute; Pepito; Cockles and Mussels; The Lonely Birch Tree; Annie Laurie; Valencinita; Beyond the Mountains; Go to Sleep; [illegible]; Dear Father-[illegible] Farewell; Cherry Blossom; Coconut and Banana; Lullaby of the Shepherd; Blues; Somebody Else to Take My Place; I Wonder What’s [illegible] of Sally; Brahm’s Lullaby; White Christmas; You’ll Never Walk Alone; Because; The Drunken Sailor; Blow the Man Down; Beyond the Sea; Rhapsody in Blue; [illegible]; Piano Concerto in B Flat; Sari Waltz; Adios, Margueuta Linda; La Bamba de Vera Cruz; Prisoners Del Mar; Begin the Beguine; It’s Easy When You Know How; Ay, Ay, Ay; Harping on a Harp; Side 2: Night and Day; Make Believe; Ol’ Man River; Smoke Gets in Your Eyes; Who?; Claire de Lune; Hungarian Rhap. No. [illegible]; Fantasy on Chopsticks; If I Could Tell You; On Wings of Song; The Last Chord; The Lords Prayer; Oh Holy Night; The Virgin Slumber Song; St. Olaf Choir; [illegible]; Lullaby on Christmas Eve; The Rosary; The Bells of St. Marys; Thine Alone; When You’re Away; Ah, Sunset Mystery of Life; I’m Falling in Love; Make Believe; Smoke Gets in Your Eyes; Merry Widow Waltz
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #13], fraser_je_041; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)